Catherine Viviano Gallery Records
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1939-1985, Series 2:; (Boxes 3-6; 5.5 linear feet)
  - General Correspondence, 1939-1985, 2.1:
    - James, Edward - Jennings, Oliver B., 1951-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
      James, Edward
      Jansen, Horst
      Jaques, Willard K.
      Jay, Mrs. N. D.
      Jean, Marcel
      Jefferson, Blanche
      Jeffress, Arthur
      Jennings, Oliver B.
    - Jensen, Dale - Johnson, Ben, 1955-1975 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      Jensen, Dale
      Jessup, John C. (Jessup, Inc. Antiques)
      Joerg, Ernest, A.
      Johansen, Mary Lee
      Johnson, Ben
    - Johnson, E. Dudley - Jones, Jane, 1955-1972, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
      Johnson, E. Dudley
      Johnson, Elaine
      Johnson, Marguerite
      Johnson, Philip
      Jones, Alfred E., Jr.
      Jones, Jane
    - Jordan, E. B. - Julian, Ruth, 1958-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
      Jordan, E. B.
      Josephs, Emmanuel and Esta
      Judkins, Donald W. (First National Bank of Minneapolis Art Committee)
      Julian, Ruth, (North Carolina State Art Society, Winston Salem Division)
    - Jurin, Benjamin - Justina, William, 1951-1974, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
      Jurin, Benjamin
      Just, Gerald (Galerie December)
      Justina, William
    - Kachadoorian, Zubal - Kaplan, Julian M., 1955-1978, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
      Kachadoorian, Zubal (Art Institute of Chicago)
      Kahn, Max
      Kahn, Rabbi Robert I. (Congregation Emanuel El)
      Kaiden, Nina
      Kalla, Erwin
      Kammerer, Renata (R. R. Bowker Co.)
      Kaplan, Julian M.
    - Karpel, Bernard - Kayaloff, Jacques and Ania, 1953-1976, undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Karpel, Bernard
      Kasle, Leonard
      Kassalow, E. M.
      Kayaloff, Jacques and Ania
    - Kelleher, Joseph and Marion,1950-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Kelly, Leon - Kepenyes, Pál, 1954-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Kelly, Leon
      Kelly, Nina
      Kemper, R. Crosby, Jr.
      Kemper, William T.
      Kent, Julie
      Kent, Seymour Murray
      Kepenyes, Pál
    - Kern, Russell B. - Kienast, H. W., 1958-1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
      Kern, Russell B.
      Kessler, Charles S.
      Kestenbaum, Mrs. Meyer
      Kienast, H. W.
    - Kimble, Gregory A. - Kinkel, Hans, 1953-1965, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
      Kimble, Gregory A.
      Kimbrough, Emily
      King, Laura (Mrs. Rufus King)
      Kinkel, Hans
    - Kissner, Franklin, 1953-1979, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Klayf, Bernard S. - Kosmin, Linda, 1957-1975, undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
      Klayf, Bernard S.
      Kleiman, Gary S.
      Klingensmith, Nancy (Harry N. Abrams, Inc.)
      Knox, Seymour (Seymour Knox Foundation)
      Koenigsberg, Mr.
      Kondolf, George
      Koppel, Joseph
      Kosmin, Linda
    - Kramer, Helen and Milton - Kreutz, Mrs. Irving W., 1948-1975, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Kramer, Helen and Milton
      Kramer, Hilton
      Krauss, Robert
      Kreeger, Mr. and Mrs. David
      Kresberg, Dr. Benjamin
      Krieger, David
      Krieger, Regine Tessier
      Kreutz, Mrs. Irving W.
    - Krugier, David - Kuh, Katharine, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      Krugier, David
      Kuh, Katharine
    - Lackner, Stephan - Langley, Charles, 1953-1970 (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Lackner, Stephan
      Laddey, Virginia H.
      Lamberson, Ralph
      Lambert, Phyllis
      Landeau, Serge
      Lange, Jonathan
      Langley, Charles
    - Langston, Mildred J. - Laurents, Arthur, 1951-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
      Langston, Mildred J. (Langston and Company)
      Lanyon, Lilian
      Lapham, Lewis
      Lauder, Ronald
      Laughlin, James (New Directions)
      Laurens, Charles
      Laurents, Arthur
    - Lavanoux, Maurice - Le Bel, John Frederic, 1951-1977 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      Lavanoux, Maurice
      Lawrence, Seymour (The Atlantic Monthly Press)
      Lazarus, Celia and Fred
      Lazarus, Paul
      Leavy, Morton L.
      Le Bel, John Frederic
    - Lee, Amy Francis - Leffler, Roy, 1961-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Lee, Amy Francis
      Lee, Paul
      Leeds, Harold
      Leembruggen, C. J.
      Leffler, Roy
    - Lefton, Al Paul - Lenox Hill Hospital, 1954-1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Lefton, Al Paul
      Lemaire, Eleanor
      Lenox Hill Hospital
    - Leonard, L. P. - Levy, Julian, 1950-1965, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Leonard, L. P.
      Lerner, Abram (Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden)
      Lesser, John and Marjorie
      Lessore, Helen (Beaux Arts Gallery)
      Levick, Mildred (Mrs. Irving Levick)
      Levin, Jeanne L. (Mrs. Isidore Levin)
      Levin, Kevin
      Levin, Sam
      Levin, Stanley
      Levy, Julian (Julian Levy Gallery)
    - Levy, Margaret - Lewis, Etta (Mrs. Samuel Lewis), 1953-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Levy, Margaret
      Levy, Richard W.
      Lewin, Charles J.
      Lewis, David (Urban Design Associates)
      Lewis, Etta (Mrs. Samuel Lewis)
    - Li, Yao T. - Lincoln, John, 1952-1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Li, Yao T.
      Libaw, William
      Liberman, Alexander
      Lieberman, William (Museum of Modern Art, New York)
      Liedholm, Mr. and Mrs. Wilhelm
      Lincoln, John
    - Linder, Bertram N. - Lizzola, Gino, 1954-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Linder, Bertram N.
      Lindsay, Mrs. John
      List, Mrs. Albert
      Littler, Dorothy
      Lizzola, Gino
    - Llach-Hill, Roberto - Logan, Drew, 1954-1976, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Llach-Hill, Roberto
      Lloyd, Mrs.
      Locker, Theodore
      Logan, Drew
    - Loges, Lynn - Lowry, Gerhard, 1952-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Loges, Lynn
      London, George
      Look Magazine
      Lorenz, Marianne
      Lo Savio, Betty
      Lotz, Steve
      Louchein, Joseph (State of New York, Department of Social Welfare)
      Lowman, Patricia (Thames and Hudson Ltd.)
      Lowry, Gerhard
    - Lteé, Doré - Lynch, Charles, 1953-1976, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Lteé, Doré
      Lubow, Robert E.
      Lucas, Charles
      Lucas, Muriel
      Ludgin, Earle
      Ludington, Wright S.
      Lux, Gwen
      Lynch, Charles
    - MacIver, Loren and Lloyd - Marx, Hilde, 1949-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
      MacIver, Loren and Lloyd
      MacMillan, Donald
      Maddux, Marzone
      Maestro, Marcello
      Mangravite, Peppino
      Marlowe, Sylvia
      Marx, Hilde (New School for Social Research)
    - Matisse, Jackie (Mrs. Bernard Monnier) - McCray, Porter, 1954-1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Matisse, Jackie (Mrs. Bernard Monnier)
      May, Morton D.
      Mazoh, Stephen
      McArthur, Mr. and Mrs.
      McAshan, S. M. Mrs.
      McCall, Ronald
      McCowas, Rhoda
      McCray, Porter
    - McGee, Bimi - McRae, Margaret, 1950-1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      McGee, Bimi
      McGlynn, Tom
      McLane, Reverend James L.
      McLarty, Jack
      McLarty, Mr.
      McLean, Jane
      McRae, Margaret (Grolier, Inc.)
    - Meech, Nanette - Melamid, Abraham, 1958-1966, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Meech, Nanette
      Meigs, Mary
      Melamid, Abraham
    - Melton, Fred - Meo, Salvatore, 1950-1976, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Melton, Fred
      Melton, Mildred H. (Secretary to Florence Knoll Bassett)
      Meltzer, Doris (Doris Meltzer Gallery)
      Menocal, Anne Stroud
      Menotti, Gian Carlo
      Meo, Salvatore
    - Metropolis, Nicholas - Midgette, Willard F., 1952-1964, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Metropolis, Nicholas
      Meyer, Norman
      Midgette, Willard, F. (Reed College)
    - Miller, James Francis, Mr. and Mrs. - Miller, Stephen Robson, 1959-1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Miller, Mr. and Mrs. James Francis
      Miller, John P.
      Miller, Mary Francis S. (Holiday Magazine)
      Miller, Milton H.
      Miller, Samuel
      Miller, Stephen Robson
    - Millman, Norma - Minske, Juergen, 1953-1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Millman, Norma
      Millonzi, Robert I.
      Mills, Barbara (Mrs. Robert Mills)
      Millstone, David
      Minkse, Juergen
    - Miro, Joan - Molloy, Caroline, 1950-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Miro, Joan
      Mitchell, Austin
      Mitchell, Charles
      Moffitt, John
      Molleda, Mercedes
      Molloy, Peter and Caroline
    - Montague, Laura B. (Mrs. Archer Montague) - Moore, Marianne, 1950-1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Montague, Laura B. (Mrs. Archer Montague)
      Moore, Fanny H. (Mrs. Paul Moore)
      Moore, Irene
      Moore, Marianne
    - Morandi, Giorgio - Morrice, David, 1950-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Morandi, Giorgio
      Mordo, Juana (Galeria Juana Mordo)
      Morelock, Max M.
      Moreni, Mattia
      Morgan, George
      Morrice, David
    - Morrow, Barbara - Mowers, Fanchon Brown, 1954-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Morrow, Barbara
      Moscowitz, Marilyn (Mrs. Morris Moscowitz)
      Moses, Charles
      Moshier, Alice (Skidmore College, Department of Art)
      Mowers, Fanchon Brown
    - Moyens, Marc, 1951-1971, undated, (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 22-24)
    - Münch, W. - Munsterberg, Hugo, 1958-1967, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Münch, W.
      Munseith, John Carl
      Munson, Larem B. (Munson Gallery)
      Munsterberg, Hugo
    - Murphy Ann C. - Myles, Morton, 1949-1978 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Murphy, Ann C. (Harper's Bazaar Magazine)
      Murray, Haya
      Music, Antonio
      Mutti, Julia (Mrs. Charles Chase Mutti)
      Myers, John Bernard (Tibor de Nagy Gallery)
      Myles, Morton
    - N. W. Ayer - Neale, Russell F., 1953-1966 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      N. W. Ayer
      Nabokoff, Nathalie
      Napoli, Giuseppe
      Nathan, Emily S.
      National Council of Jewish Women, North Essex Section, "American Art at Mid-Century"
      Nay, Elisabeth
      Neale, Russell, F. (Farrar Straus, and Young, Inc.)
    - Neuberger, Roy - The New York Times, 1952-1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Neuberger, Roy
      Neumann, Morton G.
      New York Infirmary
      New York Public Library
      The New York Times
    - Newberry, John - Nordness, Lee, 1950-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Newberry, John
      Newman, Stanley (Cue Magazine)
      Nielsen, Billie
      Nochlin, Philip
      Nordness, Lee
    - O'Boyle, John W. - Odets, Mr., 1954-1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      O'Boyle, John
      O'Boyle, Kathy (Sarah Lawrence College)
      O'Boyle, William
      Odets, Mr.
    - Odoroff, Minnie - Orlando, Ruggero, 1950-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Odoroff, Minnie
      Offin, Charles Z.
      Orengo Turati Editori
      Orlando, Ruggero
    - Orswell, Lois - Ott, Lyn, 1954-1973, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Orswell, Lois
      Orton, Noi
      Osborn, Robert
      Osborne-Hill, Timothy and Nancy
      Ossorio, Alfonso
      Osver, Arthur (Washington University, School of Fine Arts)
      Ott, Lyn
    - Owtram, Gwen, 1955-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - Paalin, Luchita - Paley, William S., 1949-1968 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Paalin, Luchita
      Packard, David
      Paddock, Barry
      Pagliacci, Aldo
      Pagnini, Marcello
      Painter, Carl W.
      Palavicini, Federico
      Paley, William S.
    - Palmer, Fred L. - Pelton, Dorothy Lee, 1955-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Palmer, Fred L.
      Palmer, Herbert B.
      Palochik, Karen (Prentice-Hall)
      Panza, Giuseppe
      Paul, Ethel S.
      Pellegrino, Jeanne
      Pelton, Dorothy Lee (Missouri Historical Society)
    - Pendleton, James B. - Peril, Barry R., 1955-1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Pendleton, James B.
      Pennock, J. Liddon
      Peril, Barry R.
    - Perlmutter, Milton - Petrassi, Goffredo, 1952-1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
      Perlmutter, Milton
      Peterfreund, Liz
      Peters, Fritz
      Peters, Penelope C.
      Petrassi, Goffredo
    - Pezzotto, Rose - Pincus, Isidore, 1951-1957, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Pezzotto, Rose
      Phillips, Duncan
      Phinney, Marian H. (Mrs. Charles Phinney)
      Picarello, Frank, E., Jr.
      Pickering, H. Douglas
      Pierrepont, Nancy (Mrs. John Pierrepont)
      Piers, Gordon
      Pincus, Irwin
      Pincus, Isidore
    - Piper, Klaus - Pletnioff, Pierre, 1950-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Piper, Klaus
      Platt, Mr.
      Plattner, Karl
      Pletinoff, Pierre
    - Poliat, David - Poor, Bernie, 1958-1973, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Poliat, David
      Pollock, Raphael C.
      Pomeroy, Ralph
      Ponder-Greene, Drew
      Poor, Bernie
    - Pope, Gayle - Price, Vincent, 1952-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Pope, Gayle
      Popper, Mrs. Robert
      Porter, Frank H.
      Potts Family
      Price, Vincent
    - Prieto, Antonio - Quackenbush, Frank, 1957-1960, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Prieto, Eugenia (Mills College Art Gallery)
      Providence Art Club
      Quackenbush, Frank
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1939 - 1973, undated, (7 folders) (Box 5, Folder 44-50)
    - Rabb, Irving - Rallo, Joseph, 1960-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
      Rabb, Irving
      Radbaugh, Bill
      Rallo, Joseph
    - Randall, G. W. and Edwina - Rathbone, Perry, 1953-1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Randall, G. W. and Edwina
      Randall, Tony
      Rasmusen, Henry N.
      Rathbone, Perry (Museum of Fine Arts, Boston)
    - Rathke, Ewald - Reed, Elizabeth Stewart, 1951-1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Rathke, Ewald
      Rauh, Harriet (Mrs. Frederick Rauh)
      Rauschenbusch, Helmut (International Directory of the Arts)
      Reed, Elizabeth Stewart (Mrs. John Reed)
    - Regalado, Ernesto, Ellen, María Marta, and Tomas, 1965-1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Regensburg, Mrs. M. E. - Rickey, Edith and George, 1952-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
      Regensburg, Mrs. M. E.
      Reifenberg, Benno
      Revson, Martin
      Ribicoff, Belle Krasne
      Ricci, Leonardo
      Riccio, John Mrs.
      Rickey, Edith and George
    - Rieti, Elsie - Ripley, Dwight, 1950-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Rieti, Elsie
      Riley, Virginia S. (Mrs. Lawrence Riley)
      Ring, Kathy
      Ripley, Dwight
    - Ritchie, Andrew and Jane - Robinson, Ione, 1951-1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
      Ritchie, Andrew and Jane
      Roach, John C.
      Roberts, Isabel and Lawrence
      Roberts, Russell
      Robinson, Ione
      Robinson, John David
    - Robinson, Mary Turley - Rodgers, Dorothy (Mrs. Richard Rodgers), 1950-1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
      Robinson, Mary Turley
      Rochon, Mrs. Edwin Water
      Rockefeller, Laurence
      Rockefeller, Nelson
      Rodgers, Dorothy (Mrs. Richard Rodgers)
    - Roditi, Edouard - Rollings, H. Kelley, 1951-1969 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      Roditi, Edouard
      Rodman, Selden
      Rogers, Henry and Roz
      Rollings, H. Kelly (America West Gallery)
    - Rollo, George - Rosenman, Samuel, 1952-1973, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
      Rollo, George
      Rollo, Joe
      Romney, Richard Adams
      Root, Mr.
      Rose, Billy
      Rose, James
      Rosenbach, Mr. (Galerie Rosenbach)
      Rosenman, Samuel
    - Rosenthal, Elaine - Ross, Sally and Walter, 1952-1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      Rosenthal, Elaine
      Rosenthal, Harold
      Rosenthal, Jerry E.
      Rosenthal, Mitchell
      Rosenthal, Tony
      Ross, Sally and Walter
    - Rothner, Robert L. - Rubin, William S., 1957-1973, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
      Rothner, Robert L.
      Rubinstein, Helena
      Rubin, William S.
    - Ruggles, Marion - Russo, Margherita, 1952-1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
      Ruggles, Marion (Curator of the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. Lester Francis Avnet)
      Runyon, Cornelia (Mrs. Charles Runyon)
      Ruprecht, Mrs. William C.
      Russell, Haide (German Consul General)
      Russell, Louise (Mrs. Edward Russell)
      Russell, Vera
      Russo, Margherita
    - Rust, David E. - Ruttenberg, Janet (Mrs. Derald H. Ruttenberg), 1950-1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
      Rust, David, E.
      Ruttenberg, Janet (Mrs. Derald H. Ruttenberg)
    - Saarinen, Aline B. Loucheim - Salerno, Harriet, 1951-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
      Saarinen, Aline B. Loucheim
      Sabersky, Jane
      Sachs, Mr.
      Sager, Robert J.
      Saglio, Henry
      Saks, Henry S.
      Salerno, Dottie
      Salerno, Harriet
    - Salpeter, Mrs. Harry - Sayre, Eleanor, 1949-1967, undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
      Salpeter, Mrs. Harry
      Salvadori, Mario
      Samuels, Mrs. Molly
      Sandak, Inc.
      Sanfilippo, Antonio
      Santomano, G.
      Sarot, Hortense (formerly Mrs. Jack Kramer)
      Saunders, Silvia
      Savelli, Angelo
      Sayre, Eleanor
    - Scanga, Italo - Schlosser, Jack, 1956-1976, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
      Scanga, Italo
      Schapiro, Meyer
      Scheinman, Mrs. Peter
      Schiele, Mrs. Herbert
      Schiff, Gert
      Schinneller, James A.
      Schlosser, Jack
    - Schlumberger, Pierre - Schneider, Stanley H., 1953-1967 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      Schlumberger, Pierre
      Schmitt, Dorothy (Mrs. Ralph Schmitt)
      Schnall, Mrs. M. E.
      Schneider, Bob
      Schneider, Daniel
      Schneider, Stanley H.
    - Schniewind, Willy - Schulke, Flip, 1960-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
      Schniewind, Willy
      Schulhof, Rudolph Buck
      Schulke, Flip (Black Star Publishing Co.)
    - Schulman, Mrs. Bernard - Schweitzer, M. R., 1957-1976, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
      Schulman, Mrs. Bernard
      Schultz, Margarete
      Schultze-Bluhm, Ursula
      Schumacher, Ulrich (Samlung Sprengel)
      Schwarz, Arturo (Galleria d'arte)
      Schwartz, Gertrude
      Schwartz, Sanford
      Schweickhen, D.
      Schweitzer, M. R.
    - Scornavacca, Tony - Sekula, Denise, 1954-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
      Sconovacca, Tony
      Seff, Manuel
      Seiberling, Miss
      Sekula, Denise
    - Seeger, Stanley, circa 1951-1974, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 72-73)
    - Selden, Mrs. Percy - Seymour, Maurice and Sonia, 1951-1978, undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
      Selden, Mrs. Percy
      Selig, Manfred
      Seligman, Kurt
      Selinsky, Martha
      Selinsky, Wladimir
      Selz, Peter
      Serlin, Oscar (Oscar Serlin Productions)
      Serrano, Pablo
      Seymour, Maurice and Sonia
    - Shalom, Joseph - Shlaes, Jacquelyn M., 1954-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
      Shalom, Joseph
      Shannon, Mary Jeffrey
      Sherman, Devorah (Mrs. Saul Stuart)
      Sherry, William Grant
      Sherwood, Harry
      Shlaes, Jacquelyn M.
    - Shoenberg, John - Shure, Alan H., 1953-1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
      Shoenberg, John
      Shoenberg, Robert
      Shoenberg, Sydney
      Shopen, Kenneth
      Shore, Sara
      Show Magazine
      Shulman, Joseph
      Shure, Alan H.
    - Silverman, Barry Edward - Sirak, Howard D., 1956-1968 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      Silverman, Barry Edward
      Singer, Nancy (Mrs. James W. Singer, Jr.)
      Simpson, Mrs. Kenneth
      Simpson, William K.
      Singer Company
      Sirak, Howard D.
    - Skelton, Owen Mrs. - Slifka, Joseph, 1950-1961 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      Skelton, Mrs. Owen
      Skidmore, Owings and Merrill
      Skouras, Odyssia
      Slifka, Joseph
    - Smit, Ben - Smith, Tommy, 1958-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Smit, Ben
      Smith, Andrew B.
      Smith, Clifford
      Smith, Frances A. (Fogg Art Museum)
      Smith, Gregory B.
      Smith, Solomon Bryan
      Smith, Tommy
    - Smoller, Arnold - Solinger, David, 1960-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Smoller, Arnold
      Snaith, William
      Snow, V. Douglas
      Snyder, Margaret L.
      Soligo, Clara
      Solinger, David M.
    - Solomon, A. K. - Spazio Magazine, 1950-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Solomon, A. K.
      Somo, A.
      Sozzi, Ercole L.
      Spaeth, Eloise (Mrs. Otto Spaeth)
      Sparr, Lisa Whitney
      Spazio Magazine
    - Speigel, Rosalynde - Spiro, Harry, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Speigel, Rosalynde
      Sperling, Milton
      Spiro, Harry
    - Sprague, Edna Jane - Stanton, Arthur, 1953-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Sprague, Edna Jane
      Sprague, Marshall
      Sprenger, W. H.
      St. Joseph, Ellis
      Stanton, Arthur
    - Stanton, Frank - Stephen, Michael, 1955-1970, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Stanton, Frank
      Stapleton, Mrs. Daniel
      Steinberg, Dorothy (Mrs. Leo Steinberg)
      Steinberg, Henry
      Steinberg, Mark C.
      Stephen, Michael
    - Stern, Mr. and Mrs. Max - Stone, Maria (Mrs. Edward Durrell Stone), 1956-1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Stern, Mr. and Mrs. Max
      Stevenson, Anne H.
      Stevenson, Archie
      Stevenson, Mrs. J. J.
      Stix, Marguerite and Hugo
      Stone, Alex B.
      Stone, Allen
      Stone, Irving
      Stone, Maria (Mrs. Edward Durrell Stone)
    - Stone, Philip - Stout, George, 1952-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Stone, Philip
      Stoner, Kenneth
      Storm, Afrida
      Story, Ala
      Stout, George (Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum)
    - Stralem, Mrs. Donald - Stroud, W. B. Dixon, 1953-1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Stralem, Mrs. Donald (The Women's Committee of The Lighthouse)
      Straus, Percy S.
      Straus, Robert and Carol
      Strauss, Gerhard
      Stroud, Anne
      Stroud, Dick and Joan
      Stroud, Justine (Mrs. William Scott Stroud)
      Stroud, W. B. Dixon
    - Stuart, Maurice - Sussman, Samuel E., 1952-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Stuart, Maurice
      Studly, Adolph
      Stutson, Susanne C. (Mrs. A. C. Stutson)
      Succa, Roy J.
      Sussman, Samuel E.
    - Sutherland, Graham - Swarzenski, Hanns, 1955-1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Sutherland, Graham
      Sutton, Ione Ulrich
      Swarzenski, Hanns
    - Sweeney, James - Swords, W. J., 1953-1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Sweeney, James
      Swenson, Swen
      Swetzoff, Hyman (Swetzoff Gallery)
      Swinford, Frank W.
      Swords, W. J.
    - Tamay, Allene - Tanning, Dorothea, 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Tamay, Allene (Vogue Magazine)
      Tannahill, Robert H.
      Tanner, Allen
      Tanning, Dorothea
    - Taylor, Frances (Mrs. Erik Taylor) - Taylor, Otis, 1956-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Taylor, Frances (Mrs. Erik Taylor)
      Taylor, Josephine
      Taylor, Otis
    - Tedesco, Linde - Thompson, G. David, 1959-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Tedesco, Linde
      Tetley, Glen
      Thomas, Winston
      Thompson, G. David
    - Thompson, H. Staley - Tjeder, Gardie (Mrs. H. A. Tjeder), 1950-1964, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Thompson, H. Staley (Rinehart and Co. Inc.)
      Thomson, Lin (Rowan Trees Pavilion)
      Thrift, Walter L. (Artists Gallery)
      Ticheman, Bridget
      Tichy, Lester
      Tischler, Kenneth
      Tjeder, Gardie (Mrs. H. A. Tjeder)
    - Todd, Anderson - Truex, Van Day, 1952-1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Todd, Anderson
      Tolbert, George F.
      Toomey, Brendan
      Toscanini, Walfredo
      Truex, Van Day
    - Tucker, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph L. - Tyler, Patrick, 1956-1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Tucker, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph L.
      Tumen, Dr. and Mrs. Henry
      Turnbull, William
      Tyler, Parker
    - Uke, M. Tugrul - United States Committee of the International Association of the Plastic Arts, 1954-1963, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Uke, Tugrul, M. (Year, The Annual Picture History)
      Unione Nazionale Per Lotta Contro L'Analfabetismo (Friends of UNLA)
      United Nations Tribute and International Art Festival
      United States Committee of the International Association of Plastic Arts
    - Urban Servicing Company - Utescher, Gerd, 1952, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Urban Servicing Company
      Utescher, Gerd
    - Valentin, Curt - Van Veen, Stuyvesant, 1951-1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Valentin, Curt
      Valsecchi, Marco (Aldo Palazzi editore)
      Van Der Rohe, Georgia
      Van Veen, Stuyvesant